ple.com.au 2019-12-06

# Privacy Policy | PLE Computers

This is the PLE Computers Privacy Policy, a document which outlines PLE Computers use of your personal information when buying and using PLE Computers Products and Services. 

  1. PLE Computers uses and may disclose your personal information in order to: 
    1. Provide products and services to you;
    2. Research, develop, administer, protect and improve our products and services;
    3. Instigate debt collection;
    4. Investigate potential fraudulent activity; and
    5. Comply with legal compulsion such as a court order.
  2. Other than listed in Clause 1, PLE Computer will not provide any information which you give us to any other organization or individual without your express permission. 
  3. All customers may request access to the personal details collected by PLE Computers in relation to themselves. PLE Computers wishes to ensure that such details are always correct and up to date and will amend any inaccuracies or changes to details on request. 
  4. By law, PLE Computers must retain some customer's details for a minimum of 5 years. However, PLE Computers does not retain customers' personal information longer than is necessary for the purposes of compliance with the law and routine administration. 
  5. PLE Computers keeps customer information on controlled facilities which are secured against unauthorized access. Proof of identity will be required before information is released to any person, including the customer. 
  6. PLE Computers runs an email list, this email list will be used to communicate newsletters, specials, product information or notices regarding PLE Computers operations. By dealing with PLE Computers you will be subscribed to the email list. Should you wish to subscribe or unsubscribe your email address, you may do this through our website (http://www.ple.com.au) or by clicking Unsubscribe at the bottom of our newsletter. 
  7. PLE Computers is constantly improving and enhancing its products and services to customers, and may update this privacy policy from time to time. Any changes to the policy will be advised to customers in our regular newsletter and/or by updating this page on the PLE Computers website. 
  8. **Do we use cookies?** Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business. 
  9. **Remarketing** We also uses 3rd party vendor re-marketing tracking cookies, including the Google Adwords tracking cookie. This means we will continue to show ads to you across the internet, specifically on the Google Content Network (GCN). As always we respect your privacy and are not collecting any identifiable information through the use of Google’s or any other 3rd party remarketing system. The third-party vendors, including Google, whose services we use – will place cookies on web browsers in order to serve ads based on past visits to our website. – Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to your website. This allows us to make special offers and continue to market our services to those who have shown interest in our service. 
  10. If you have any queries or comments concerning the privacy policy, call PLE Computers on 08 9309 4771 or email: feedback@ple.com.au
